fleshasiadaily.com 2010-11-26

# Privacy Policy

The following privacy statement covers  FAD 3.0. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://fleshasiadaily.com/2007/07/27/contact-us-to-submit-photoslinkstips/).

**Ownership of Information**  
FAD 3.0 is the sole owner of the information collected on this website.

**Comments**  
In order to enhance their use of the FAD 3.0 website, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. FAD 3.0 reserves the right to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use.

**Mailing List**  
FAD 3.0 may launch a mailing list for some or all of the FAD 3.0 websites. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from a site’s mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular emails from the site, including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, FAD 3.0 has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by FAD 3.0 only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**  
FAD 3.0 uses third-party advertising companies including Clicksor, among others, to serve ads when you visit our websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, FAD 3.0 may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on this site.

**Business Transitions**  
In the event FAD 3.0 goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**  
The FAD 3.0 website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that FAD 3.0 is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by FAD 3.0.

**Notification of Changes**  
Whenever FAD 3.0 changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://fleshasiadaily.com/2007/07/27/contact-us-to-submit-photoslinkstips/).
